And, um,
you know, in games like this, you know,
obviously there's a little history
between the two teams.
Scored a lot of points against them last
year, um, blowout. I don't think you
anybody can can could,
you know, say that you
ran up the score on them necessarily,
but how important it is that for you to
manage that those kind of games where
you can score a lot of points on an
opponent. Like when you call off the
dogs, is it important to
I guess kind of play the game [snorts]
respectfully and
Well, I don't
Look, I don't think
I don't think of it in any of those
terms. That's not what any of that's
about. It's man, you go in with a game
plan and it's specific to that opponent.
So, if you don't use them, there's a lot
of them you may you may not use.
You may not use those plays again the
rest of season. Now, sometimes they'll
come back up because of the structure of
the defense. So, if you've got them and
you're getting first downs, you you want
to use what you got. It's as simple as
that. You're just trying to
trying to move the ball and play
football, you know? And, uh,
like it's been done to us. Um,
that's happened, you know?
Um, and but there's no ill will about
it. You're just trying to play football,
you know? And, uh,
you know, we're trying to score points.
We're trying to eliminate points. That's
what they're trying to do. They're going
to try to score as many points as they
can. I mean, I that's
there's no ill will on either side of
that, man. You you know?
You got to try to score. You got to try
to eliminate points on defense. I just
there's there's you know, for the last
week to a lot of people outside it seems
like the guy's falling, you know, the
the Thanksgiving loss and Ragnow and
Kirby and Terrion on IR now. Do you ever
do you ever feel that way and and I
guess regardless of if you do or don't,
like how do you, you know, manage to put
it in perspective after everything
that's Yeah, I don't Yeah, I don't think
in those terms. I just I I don't. I
can't. Um, I'm just That's not how I
think. Um,
the guys that we have here are here for
a reason. Uh, we got plenty of we got
plenty of talent. We got plenty of good
dudes, uh, that are made the right way.
The coaches are good.
And it's it's really about playing
winning football, you know? And it's
going to take all three phases. It takes
every guy that we have doing their job.
The margin for error is small, but it's
doable. We can do it. And, uh,
but, you know, we we got to eliminate
the things that that keep us from
winning before we can actually win the
game, you know? Before you start, uh,
battling against the opponent, you got
to quit battling against yourself. When
start that snowball the other way, you
know? Well, a win's always going to set
you in the right direction. I mean,
that's what it's about, you know? And
you can't look beyond the ones that's in
front of you. And and that's what we
have right now. It's Dallas. That's got
to be the sole focus and it's everything
that we have.
We got to di- digest this plan,
understand the opponent, understand who
you're getting ready to face. You got to
be ready to win those 101s. What's he
going to try to do to you? What are you
going to do to him?
Um,
and everybody's got to be on point. And
and that's all you worry about. And then
and then you
then you worry about the next one after
that. And the word I've probably heard
the most in the locker room this week is
urgency. Mhm. You know, when when you go
through a practice week knowing
that you really need this one, how do
how does urgency manifest itself in the
day-to-day with these players? Well, I
just think the the guys are on point.
Look, they're always that way. There
there is always a level of urgency, but
I, you know, with this unit here, this
crew, they you know, they don't like
losing. None of us like losing. And, uh,
it's a it puts a bad taste in your
mouth, you know? And, uh, and so we just
we just came off a loss, you know,
division opponent. And nobody that
we don't want that again.
Um,
so, you know, they these last two days
have been really good. The guys have
been locked in. I thought they were
flying around yesterday. Um,
so, you know, but I just bring it back.
Yes, there's urgency, but there's not
panic. You know, you start, uh, taking
this to a level of oh, we we got to oh,
then that's when guys start making
mistakes. Well, I's going to start
trying to do your job and then then I'm
out of position to do my job because I'm
trying to do your job. And that's when
it really everything breaks down.
So, just do your do your job, handle
your business, do it the best you can do
it
and be on point. Um,
you know, and eliminate those the things
that,
uh,
that require no talent, you know? The
discipline, man. The fundamentals, the
technique. You just handle that.
Terrion, is it the same shoulder that
was giving him problems earlier in the
year? And if so, when did it start
bothering him again? When did you kind
of make the decision to shut him down?
>> Yeah, yes, it is. Um, and it's
you know, it's been there. I mean, it's
not like it went away. Um,
and and it, you know, bothered him in
this game a little bit. So, um,
just felt like, you know, it was
something needed to be done.
Speak to the confidence you have in
Jameson to to to step up again.
Obviously had a great performance after
St. Brown last week, but he's really
shown that that ability to to kind of
step up in in games this year. Just the
confidence you have in him if if asked
to do so again. High confidence. High
confidence. He he's really growing. I
mean, he just continues to grow and get
better. Um,
you know, he's fearless.
He's fearless. Um,
and he's just his fundamentals, you
know, for the for the speed and
quickness he has, the ability for him to
drop his weight now and and there's
really some detail to his route. He's
becoming a hard cover. And then you see
the run after catch ability. He's had
it. Um,
so, his confidence is growing. Uh, our
confidence is growing.
And, uh, he he's he's doing well, you
know? And I mean, he came back out this
week again. I mean, he's full tilt. You
should have seen him running yesterday.
I mean, this guy he works now. He works
in practice every day. Um,
so, love where he's at. One more on
Terrion. Um,
played 1,000 snaps as a rookie. You
know, was was pretty damn durable.
Uh,
this year from camp on it seemed like
just snake bitten, you know? Different
things rotating. Left a lot of games
early. Was there anything about his
style of play or do you just chalk this
up to one of those years, bad luck? How
how do you how do you look at just his
his body of work this season? Yeah, it
it's you know, it's been frustrating,
you know? And I know it's frustrating
for him.
Um,
but no, I mean, it just it it just feels
like one of those years. I mean, I
wouldn't say there's anything out of the
norm.
Um, he did he got off to a really good
start in camp and then,
you know, the bug hit him. And then we
it just kind of was one thing to
another. Um,
but
yeah, I don't I I it's just one of those
years, you know? It's a tough year for
him. Dan, just looking around the NFL,
it seems like we've seen a couple upsets
every week this season. League maybe
more volatile than ever. How does the
the landscape of the league and the idea
that everyone might be flawed, everyone
might be beatable change the way you
view the ceiling, the outlook for your
own team?
Uh, it didn't change. Uh, I don't think
it changes anything. Um,
I know for where we're at, you know, it
just goes back to man, all you can worry
about is is what is right in front of
you. And and you got to play the best
best game that you can play
and manage this game the best that you
can, you know? We know that's a potent
offense over there. Uh, they're playing
really good defensive football. This
this D-line is strong, very strong. Um,
you know? And I just go back to this,
man. It's going to take all three
phases. We we need all three units to
step up for us and, uh, and play big.
They're hot right now. They're playing
really good football. They got a lot of
confidence. Uh, they're a rugged team,
you know? Um,
they are built off the O-line, D-line,
but they got explosiveness on the
perimeter.
Uh, and Dak's playing at a high level,
man.
Um,
so, look, we know we got our hands full,
but but we're up to the challenge. We're
up to it. And, uh, we know what's in
front of us.
And you can't worry about the other
teams that are out there, the other
teams that are in front of you or what
it looks like in the NFC. You just
can't, you know? And it doesn't matter.
It shoot, you went out, you might not
get in, but you don't know, right? Hell,
maybe it only takes 11 to get in. I
don't know, but I know this, we got to
win this one. We got to win this one.
Um,
so, let's let's worry about that right
now. Over the course of the season, like
how much do you monitor the the state of
the league, the conference, who's up,
who's down, you know?
>> I don't even look at it. Like cuz it it
The one time we did one of those was I
talked about it at the bye. I just
showed where everything was at at that
point coming right out of the bye. And
that I haven't looked at it. I haven't
thought about it, you know?
You
cuz it does no good. I mean, it does you
no good, you know? I mean, you can sit
there and hope and whatever and it
doesn't matter. We got to take care of
our business. It doesn't matter what
happens, you know? All All the right
things could happen and if you lose, it
doesn't matter, you know? So, you got to
win. You got to win. Uh, I just want to
ask about Amon-Ra. Just how is how is he
progressing and how close is he to He's
better. He's better. That's the best way
to say it, but,
um,
but I don't see him practicing today,
you know? But he is better.
You know? So, I know this about if he
can play, if he can play, he he'll play.
You know? That's the best way to say it.
Is he, uh, close to getting back at all
today or is Yeah, I mean, he's getting
better, but I don't see him this week.
One more last one. Dan, the other day
Hutch was talking about the adversity
that the team is facing and he was
saying that it's easy to be gritty when
it's when you're winning and it's all
sunshine and rainbows. Just given the
current spot that the team is in, what
can
coaches like yourself and then the
players learn about, you know, what
you're going through right now? Well,
for some of these guys, this is a
different spot that they've been in, you
know? Uh, for a guy like Hutch, he knows
what this is. St. Brown knows what this
is. Sewell knows what it is. Goff knows
what it is. Decker knows what it is. We
we got plenty that that have been
through it. And, uh,
you know? And and so,
they got an idea of what it is. And you
just and you go back to work. You put
your head down and and you clean up the
little things. And cuz the little things
are what win games in this league. So,
um,
you know? It
you know, you're sitting here, uh, two
years ago and you're doing backflips,
right? But now all of the sudden it's,
you know, with where we're at it it
feels down cuz
you know, we've we've done some pretty
good things over the last 2 years, but
you can't worry about it. And all you
can do is handle your own business,
handle your own play, uh your own
coaching, and uh
and then go out there and play the best
game you can play, execute.
Hey Dan, what one more real quickly.
Kirby got back on the practice field
yesterday. It seemed like the brace was
agitating him. I don't think it's
unusual for a guy playing with a brace,
new, but he seemed pretty down when we
talked to him in the locker room.
>> [snorts]
>> You just get a sense of how he came out
of that that return to practice.
Uh
I mean, not really. I mean, I you know,
look that's his first time to go out
there. He's been rehabbing and he's been
doing things on the side, but that's
kind of his first being around it uh in
the individual drills. And so,
you know, sometimes you're you're always
going to hope for a little bit more than
than the first time you get back on the
turf. Um
but that doesn't mean this is a setback,
you know.
Now, I know he can get frustrated, you
know, and I know it can be frustrating
when you get hurt, especially when
you've been trying to work your way
back. And he's been I mean, he's been
busting his tail to get back. So,
um but there again, you just continue to
treat it, try to eliminate the pain or
or limit most of the pain and
to where he feels like he can produce.
Yep.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Okay.